module.exports = [
  {
    id: 2, // optional
    question: " In C language, FILE is of which data type?",
    options: ["int", "char*", "struct", "None of the above"], // store options in an array
    correct: "struct",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 3, // optional
    question: "Who invented Java Programming?",
    options: [
      "Steve Jobs",
      "James Gosling",
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "James Gosling",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: " Java programming was developed by James Gosling at Sun Microsystems in 1995. James Gosling is well known as the father of Java.", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 6, // optional
    question:
      "Which type of dragon does Viktor Krum face in the first task of the Triwizard Tournament?",
    options: [
      "Hungarian Horntail",
      " Chinese Fireball",
      "Swedish Short-Snout",
      "Common Welsh Green",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Chinese Fireball",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "The Hungarian Horntail is the most dangerous of the four dragons.", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 8, // optional
    question: "Where Did It Originate:Nasi Goreng",
    options: ["Indonesia", "Bahrain", "Mexico", "Vietnam"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Indonesia",
    hint: "South-East Asian Country", // optional
    fact: "Fried rice dish, usually cooked with pieces of meat and vegetables", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 10, // optional
    question:
      "Which film series from the 2000s stars Tom Cruise as Ethan Hunt?",
    options: [
      "James Bond: Casino Royale",
      "Mission: Impossible",
      "The Bourne Identity",
      "Die Hard: Mission Impossible",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Mission: Impossible",
    hint: "This film series features high-stakes espionage missions led by a skilled agent named Ethan Hunt.", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 11, // optional
    question: "Who played Sharkboy in Sharkboy and Lavagirl?",
    options: ["Taylor Lautner", "Zac Efron", "Jake Gyllenhaal", "Shia LaBeouf"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Taylor Lautner",
    hint: "He's known for his role as a werewolf in another popular film series", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 3, // optional
    question: "Can you Guess The Food Anagram:AMOK AS US (8)",
    options: ["Soak Maus", "Souma Kas", "Moussaka", "Amass You"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Moussaka",
    hint: "A dish made with layers of eggplant, minced meat, and tomato sauce, topped with a creamy b√©chamel sauce", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 4, // optional
    question: "What is the most stolen food in the world?",
    options: ["Cheese", "Bread", "Milk", "Chocolate"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Cheese",
    hint: "Made by using milk.", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 11, // optional
    question: "True or False: Apples belong to the rose family.",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 12, // optional
    question:
      "True or False: Oysters and Lobsters used to be the food of the working class.",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 2, // optional
    question:
      "Can you name the actor who plays Darth Vader in the Star Wars movies?",
    options: ["David Prowse", "Harrison Ford", "Oscar Isaac", "John Boyega"], // store options in an array
    correct: "David Prowse",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 3, // optional
    question: "Name the teen heartthrob who played the role of Cedric Diggory.",
    options: [
      "Robert Pattinson",
      "Rupert Grint",
      "Daniel RadCliffe",
      "Tom Felton",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "Robert Pattinson",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 4, // optional
    question:
      "Which of the following dismissals is NOT a valid way to get out?",
    options: ["Bailed", "Caught", "Run Out", "Bowled"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Bailed",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 5, // optional
    question: "What is a cricket ball made of?",
    options: [
      "Rubber",
      "Leather",
      " Leather Outer/Cork Inner",
      "Leather Outer/Rubber Inner",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: " Leather Outer/Cork Inner",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 1, // optional
    question: "What is the largest dog breed in the world?",
    options: [
      "Scottish Deerhound",
      "Great Pyrenees",
      " Greyhound",
      "English Mastiff",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "English Mastiff",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 2, // optional
    question: "How many teeth do normal adult dogs have?",
    options: ["42", "36", "44", "69"], // store options in an array
    correct: "42",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 8, // optional
    question: "Where was England legend David Beckham born?",
    options: ["Manchester", "Norwich", "London", "Carlisle"], // store options in an array
    correct: "London",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 14, // optional
    question: "The SQL LIKE operator is used in which of the following clause?",
    options: ["Having", "Select", "Where", "Group by"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Where",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "The SQL LIKE operator is used in a WHERE clause to search for a specified pattern in a column.", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 12, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagrams:ENTIRE REGION",
    options: ["Erogentirn", "Tonerigern", "Girenteron", "Orienteering"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Orienteering",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 13, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagrams:SNOUT BAIL",
    options: [" Usain Bolt", "Justin Gatlin", "Allyson Felix", "Mo Farah"], // store options in an array
    correct: " Usain Bolt",
    hint: "Atheletics", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 6, // optional
    question: "True or False: You can hypnotise a chicken?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "True",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 9, // optional
    question:
      "True or False: Coral (in coral reefs) are plants and not animals?",
    options: ["Partially True", "False", "True", "Partially False"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Flse",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 10, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagram: RAPTOR",
    options: ["Parrot", "Raptor", "Trapor", "Raprot"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Parrot",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 13, // optional
    question: "Guess The Anagrams: SOCCER IDOLS",
    options: ["Crocodiles", "Crockodiles", "Socerlodes", "Idolcress"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Crocodiles",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 14, // optional
    question: "What is the name of the horse of Alexander the Great?",
    options: ["Copenhagen", "Comanche", "Bucephalus", "Chaitak"], // store options in an array
    correct: "Bucephalus",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 6, // optional
    question: "Which of the following is not javascript data types?",
    options: [
      "Null type",
      "Undefined type",
      "Number type",
      " All of the mentioned",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: " All of the mentioned",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: " JavaScript is a dynamic, loosely typed language. Variables in JavaScript aren't tied to any specific value type, and each variable can be assigned and reassigned to values of all the types", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 10, // optional
    question: "All keywords in Python are in _________",
    options: [
      "Capitalized",
      "lower case",
      "UPPER CASE",
      "None of the mentioned",
    ], // store options in an array
    correct: "None of the mentioned",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "True, False and None are capitalized while the others are in lower case.", // optional
  },
  {
    id: 11, // optional
    question:
      "Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called __________",
    options: ["pi", "anonymous", "lambda", "none of the mentioned"], // store options in an array
    correct: "lambda",
    hint: "", // optional
    fact: "Python supports the creation of anonymous functions (i.e. functions that are not bound to a name) at runtime, using a construct called lambda. Lambda functions are restricted to a single expression. They can be used wherever normal functions can be used.", // optional
  },
];
